Thank you for watching%0Aoi Hey, where the hell are you%0Aoi Have you ever had a shot of Ofudesaki Blackbeard's kitty? I have%0A-Aoi%0Aoi I haven%0Aoi%0Aoi, no? You don%0Aoi know the rules? I know the rules%0A-Aoi, but the original rule of "Blackbeard's Kitty Ippatsu" is that the first person to stab the sword loses, but today's rule is the opposite: the first person to stab wins. But today it's the other way around%0A so whoever flies away wins%0A B-Beans%0A-Aoi, you find one, you come back here and stab it%0A-Aoi, and repeat%0A-Aoi, great%0A-Aoi, there are 24 holes in Blackbeard's kitty%0A-Aoi, that's not even enough%0A-Aoi, there are only 4 left%0A-Aoi, so I'll explain the rules first%0A-Aoi, and then I'll announce the locations later%0A-Aoi, and then I'll tell you where the other 4 holes are%0A-Aoi. We'll announce the locations later%0A A.A. You can take as many of those four as you want and bring them back here%0A A.A. We haven't told you where the other 16 are yet%0A A.A. We can't tell you where the other 16 are now%0A A.A. So%0A A.A., if you rent eight of them and they haven't flown yet%0A A.A., we'll announce the locations%0A A.A. And here's another rule%0A since this is a trip for both of you%0A you can eat whatever you want%0A but if you eat one soft serve ice cream for example%0A that counts as one. You will have to do one good thing per day for the total number of ice creams you ate%0A and you will have to keep raising the story for that number of days%0A. So that's it for the rules%0A. Start%0Aoi Wow%0Aoi, what %0Aoi, it's not here, is it? %0A-Aoi, come on, let's give up%0Aoi, it's in your pocket%0Aoi, it's not in there? %0A-Aoi, eh%0Aow! %0A I found it! %0A hey! Hey! Hey! Yeah! %0AWell, if you stab it, it'll give you a hint%0Aand if you stab Miyu, he'll give you a hint%0Are you sure? %0Are you going to do it? %0AYeah%0AOh, you'll stop%0AYes%0AWell, I'll give you a hint%0AABut isn't Beans your sacred place now? %0AYes. Are you tired? %0AYes, I'm tired%0AI'm tired%0Aof course it's in a place that concerns you all%0AWhat, are you going alone? %0AWhere are you going? %0AIs this place open? It won't open%0AIt's this way, isn't it? %0ANext time I'll show you%0Aare you all right now? Do you have the red sword? %0AI don't have it%0AI thought%0Athank you very much%0AI don't have it%0AEh, I don't have it%0AI don't have it%0ANo%0ANo%0AI don't think so%0AI don't have it...%0AEh, are you sure you have it hidden? %0AYou've hidden it%0Awhat? %0AIt's there! %0AIt's there! %0AIt's there! %0AYes! I%0Am going! %0AI don%0At%0At%0At%0At%0At%0At%0At%0As hard as it is%0At%0At%0Am not%0At%0At%0As easy%0A let%0As I give you this%0Aplease buy three more%0Aplease buy%0Aplease buy this one%0Aplease buy this one too%0Aokay%0Ait's a blue jade%0As we celebrate our 4th blue jade anniversary%0As you know Taokusa is like a blue jade? Isn%0At the mention of Taokun, isn%0At the mention of blue balls? %0AIt%0As a blue ball%0As there%0As a possibility that Rinne has one%0AIf she doesn%0At least three more%0Awe need to go see how many more%0Awe don%0Ahave? %0AKage! I'm gonna stab it! Ready! I%0Ajust%0Awant%0A quick check of how many we%0Are%0Asking%0Aabout%0Ah! %0A-Neither of you are sticking%0A-how did you find it? %0Ahe said he was running away%0AI wonder where he went? Excuse me, sir,%0Are you carrying a sword? %0A sword? Excuse me%0Apardon me%0Awhere is it? %0AI knew it%0Awasn%0At a glance%0AI can't find it%0AI think I'll go upstairs%0Aon the second floor above%0ABy the way, I haven't been able to split up here very often%0AI'd like to introduce each costume and whose costume it is%0AWhat? %0AThese are the clothes of KAYA's unit%0Athey are the clothes we wore for the hall image shoot%0Ahere it is! %0An extra%0A! %0An added bonus%0AIt%0As definitely coming from there%0AI%0Awill fast forward%0Awhy? %0AYes%0AYeah%0ABy the way, a certain person has a hint, and Hitami talked with him a while ago. %0AMiyu talked to him too. %0AWhat do you mean? %0AI thought you would have found it by now. %0AWhat? %0AWhat? Did you lie? %0AAAh, go lock the door%0Ah, don't you have it? %0AAaaaah! I've got it! %0AYou have it%0AI'm sorry%0AI was wearing it%0AI'm off%0AWhat? %0AWho are you talking to? %0AOh. %0ANow you have all four Bee Beans. %0ANext, I will announce where the four beeves are all together. %0AActually, only Mr. Fujitani has been there. %0AOh! %0A Australia. %0A Mr. Beagle? %0AYes. %0AIt's true! %0AI've been there. %0AIt was true. %0AOh, no, I haven't. %0AIt wasn't a blur. %0AI'll come back for the overseas section. %0AOkay, I understand. %0AThere is a secondhand clothing store called Beagle, where we did the secondhand clothing project, but Mr. Fujitani did not go there.%0AThere are four of them there. %0And those four bottles come back one by one, so you don't have to stick them in. %0AYou must be Mr. Beagle. %0Are you taking a break? %0ANo, that's it. %0ANo, sir. %0AI'm just thinking of a plan. I don't have a brain. %0Are you sure you want to leave right now, Mr. Beagle? %0AI need to think of a plan before I go. %0Anyone else, Mr. Beagle? %0AThe rest of Mr. Beagle will tell me when he's done. %0AYeah. %0All right, let's go. %0Agood to go. %0AYes, let's go. %0ABye-bye. %0AYay! %0AYes, so we're here! %0AWe're here! %0AYay! %0Ah, you know that vintage clothing store%0Ah, Eten? %0AI know it! %0AOh my gosh%0AI'll look for it on the left hand side then! As a handicap%0AThank you! %0Another four for Mr. Beagle! Can I%0A eat them? %0AYou can%0Aleave it up to me%0AYou leave it up to me%0AYou have Anna here today%0AI haven't met you before, Tami-San. I%0Ave never met you before,%0A but it%0As nice to meet you,%0A Katsuro and Anna are a couple who run this store,%0A and they are doing a wonderful job! Mr. Katsuro%0A is not here today%0A so we had to go in and see him! %0AAnd so we go inside! %0AThe moment the door opens, it's time to get started%0AOkay%0Ahello! It%0As been a long time! %0AWell, I'll be looking for you%0Aplease look for me! %0AI found it! %0AWhat? Cute outfit%0Alook for it%0Aand let me know once you find it in Japan%0Aand I'll give it to you if you play rock-paper-scissors-paper with me%0Aand I'll give it to you if you buy it%0ANow, here we go! who did you buy it from%0Ait took you so long%0Athank you%0AYay%0AI'm glad I did%0AI want to stay longer%0AI'm so glad I took a little stroll around the store%0AYeah%0AI'm not in my fall clothes%0AI'm so cute%0AI'm out of fall clothes now%0AI think the one I'm wearing looks warmer%0ANo, I don't want to wear this every day%0A 0ANo, I don't want to do this every day%0AIt's cute%0AIt's a four-letter word%0AIt's not a four-letter word%0AIt's a four-letter word%0AIf you start looking at it, it's over%0AAThe glass is cute%0AThank you%0AI like it and it's a problem%0AWell, I'm going to the inspection station now%0AI never thought I'd be able to do it once Are you going back to Ebean's%0AThank you%0AThank you too%0AI'm glad you were found safe%0AWe'll be waiting for you again%0AThank you%0AI came back to Ebean's just for this%0AYay%0Adon't you want to go home? %0AAwe'd like to do one at a time%0Aso let's play rock-paper-scissors%0Aand we'll start with par%0Aand rock-paper-scissors%0Aand we lost%0Aand we'll go on%0Aand we'll go on%0Aand we won't stop%0Aand we'll do one at a time%0Aand we've done that%0Aand now you've got the rest. You%0Ahave no choice%0About going for the rest%0ANothing more%0Athen here it is%0AOh, I'm going for this one%0A. %0ASo, since I didn%0At fly, I%0Am going to have to go get the rest of the tickets%0Asouvenir tickets! %0A wide ticket! %0AI have%0A16 remaining tickets%0Aand I actually have%0A16 of them hidden%0Ain two places%0A8 and 8%0AOh, that's a lot%0Aso we should probably split up and go get them%0About time we announce the location! %0AYes! %0AFirst one is Mr. Katsu Abe%0AOh~! %0AYou have been a great help%0AOne more place is Mr. Kei Ishinuma, a wood shop%0AOh~! %0AI've never been there%0AI'm indebted to you! %0AWhere would you like to go? %0AWhat? Since you've never been to the wood shop%0AI'll go with Katsu Abe%0AYes, let's go! %0AYes! %0AYay! %0AThere's a time break. Yay! %0AI'm so thirsty%0Acan you two tell me how many each of you bought? %0AYes,%0AI got two macaroons and two strawberry milk%0AI got a banana rich, a macaroon and a bulgogi%0Athe roof top trigger dancer%0ARine got two and Miyu got three%0Aso it's decided that the loser will get 5 days to post their instagram%0Aso we'll take a break But... So we are going to take a break%0Abut after we eat we will leave%0Aso we are taking a break today%0AThank you for watching%0AWhich would you rather have if you could only eat sweet food for the rest of your life%0Aor if you could only eat salty food for the rest of your life? %0ASo here it is%0Asweet%0Aand%0Asweet! Definitely salty! %0Anyone in the group who would choose sweet? %0AYes, there is%0Athis person is salty%0AI think this picture is unusual%0Ahe chooses sweet%0AI think this picture is unusual%0AIt's cute, please come%0ALet's go%0AI'm Nobuyo Oyama%0AI'm talking about Okada-san%0Awe're on our way to Abekatsu Jidosha in Ishinomaki%0A AIf you go to Abekatsu Jidosha you can get 8 swords%0AI have to get them quickly and come back%0AI'll do my best%0AI'm on my way%0ABye-bye%0AI've arrived at Abekatsu-san%0AI'll ask him if he has a sword%0Ahe escaped%0AHello%0Ado you have a sword? Do you have a sword? %0AYes,%0AI have one? %0And seven more? I%0Ahave%0Aother%0A5 swords! What? Three more bottles%0AWhat? Why? %0AYou're coming out one at a time, style%0AAAre there two more bottles somewhere%0Awhere are the two more bottles? %0Ah! %0A look! %0AI found them! %0AWhere? %0AOh! %0AOh, there it is! %0AAmazing! %0AI got eight! %0As we're going to be on the show, I'd like to introduce myself%0AI hear you're nervous%0AI'd like to tell you my name%0AI'm Sho Yoshida from Ame-Activist%0AI'm Sho Yoshida%0AWhat's your favorite food? %0AYour favorite food is ramen%0Aramen! %0AOppe-chan says%0Ait's really good%0AThank you very much%0AI'm going to change myself%0AWow what's this face%0AThis face is terrible%0ALook at it%0AI'm going to go%0Ahmmm! %0AI've finished drawing%0AWow! %0AI've never drawn anything this big%0AYay! %0AThank you! Yay! %0AI heard a rumor that there is a line of signed CDs on the street now%0Aso they are going to send them to me in this car! %0AWow! %0AWell, I'm on my way! %0AYes! Oh! Oh, wow! %0AWe're here! %0AWow! All the...%0AZoom...zoom...zoom...%0AWow, great! I%0Ajust wrote something here too%0AI'm so happy%0AWhy do they sell dumplings%0Abecause they don't sell dumplings over there? %0ABecause they%0Am eating canned food over there%0Abut we didn%0At think this was possible%0Aweren%0At least it's okay, right? I%0Am buying, then I'll buy dumplings%0Athank you%0Athank you very much%0Asee%0AI just left Abe Katsudo%0AI don't know where the dog is now%0AI'll try to catch up%0As for you%0As for me%0As for you%0As for you%0As for you...%...%. 0AYay! %0AI arrived yesterday morning! I finally arrived%0Aand I want to find it as soon as possible, so I'm going inside now! %0ALet's go! %0AWelcome%0As always...! Oh my...%0A Wow! Oh, my God! So many cans! %0A Tomo's! Please buy these! Absolutely! %0AYou'll definitely buy them! Hey! %0AI want to see it once! %0AWhen everyone else was here, they were looking for canned goods of their choice%0AWhat! I want to find it! %0AIs this the most famous one%0AYes, it is. When I think of Ki-no-ya, I think of whales%0AI'm really interested in these two I found%0AI'll go with these two! I've decided on you! %0AI'll have the whale ajillo and the whale waahijo! %0AYeah! %0Are you sure you want to buy these? %0ANo problem! %0AYay! %0Aplease take this one! Thank you very much! %0AI got it! I got it! I'm so happy! %0AYou should buy them! Please buy my two names! %0All right, let's go! %0A Aren't you forgetting something? %0AKenrah! %0A Oh, no! Mew's gonna beat me! %0A Oh, no! %0Am I here today looking for Ken? %0AI have something that looks like a can that you left with me%0Acan? %0AYes. %0Are there three in total that you kept for me? You might want to open them%0Are you sure you don't want to open them all? Can I open them all? %0AOkay%0ANow we're going to open%0Ait's empty%0ANo, this is it%0AI'll open this one%0AWater%0AIt's all prepared%0AHere it is%0AOh, there it is! %0AThank you very much! %0AI found it, guys! %0ASo I%0Am going to take this with me back to Evie's! %0ALet's go! %0AHey! %0Are you ready? %0AYou just got here? %0AWhat? What did you buy? I went to Abukatsu and they had dumplings on sale%0Aand I thought you were lying%0ANo way! %0AI'm telling you the truth%0Abefore you stab me with your sword%0AI bought 38 of them in red%0Aand they turned red%0As I was surprised%0AI was surprised%0AI was amazed%0AI bought a whale guajillo%0Aand a whale ajillo%0Aand ajillo%0Awhat is that%0Aand here we go%0A AI'll do it here%0AI'm so surprised%0AI'm scared%0AI'm going%0Await, please really%0Aplease fly%0Aplease%0Acall me%0Anon%0Awhat a surprise it didn't fly so we pulled out all our swords and had them spread out in a battle of expressions. %0AWe%0Awill do a circular bat lineup of circular swords%0Aand then the two of us will settle this once and for all%0At the final stage, let%0As they are scattered, let%0As fight to the end%0Aplease%0Ayay! %0ALet's get started%0A1%0A2%0A3%0A4%0A5%0A6%0A7%0A9%0A10%0A Wow! %0AWhere, where, where? %0Awhere is it, where is it, where is it%0Aplease fly away%0Aand don%0At fly away%0Awah! %0AOh, it fell out%0AOh, no good%0Ahead%0Awhere%0Ait was%0Atwice%0AYes%0Aahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha%0A  life%0Ais starting%0Ayay%0AI'm glad I worked hard today%0AI'm going to work hard every day%0Afrom today%0Afor the next %0A8 days%0As long as you don%0At take pictures%0Ae%0Aevery day%0Am going to take pictures%0Aevery day%0Aso please%0Am going to do %0Aone good thing a day%0Athat day%0Awow%0AI'm going to work hard%0Awow%0A %0ASo%0Athat%0As you know%0Athank you%0Afor your hard work%0Ait%0As like the last episode%0Aand not%0Alike the good work you%0Ahave%0Added%0Agood button%0Aand%0Ayes%0Awe%0Advish you%0Ato take this Blackbeard quiz%0Ayes%0At least try%0At least try%0Ato take this quiz. Please try it%0AThank you%0AThank you very much%0ABye%0AAah I'm tired%0AWow%0A[Please subscribe to our channel].
undefined